tvgorge.com 2010-04-08

# Privacy Policy - TVGorge.com

## TVGorge Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the TVGorge website ("Site"). We regard your privacy seriously and provide this Privacy Policy to describe which information we collect and how we use it. 

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)** You may use this Site without registering. You may also register and voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (?PII?), such as your name and email address. When you create your account, we will ask you to create a username and password. You will be able to enter PII into your password-protected account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and your account information. In addition, TVGorge allows you to set up personal profiles that may be viewed by all Site users. To enrich your experience, you may choose to include some PII in your public profile so that other users can identify you. You can change or delete your profile anytime. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** We may collect non-personally identifiable information (?Non-PII?) such as your internet protocol address and information associated with your computer, browser and network to deliver services or information, provide notices, track usage, verify your authority to use the Site, store your preferences, and generally improve the content and functionality of the Site. We may also use small text files stored in your browser called cookies to store your preferences, record session information, and improve Site experience. We associate cookies with your browser, not with the information to PII you submit in your account. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. 

**Disclosure** We will not intentionally disclose PII in your account except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy. Non-PII may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements. We may also disclose your PII and Non-PII if we believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, or to prevent harm to yourself or others. In addition, we may transfer your PII to a successor entity upon a change of control of TVGorge, sale, merger, other corporate reorganization. Such successor entity will be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**Email** Email addresses are used for identification, inviting new friends to TVGorge, searching for and finding friends, for general communication, and to send notifications to you. To facilitate searching for and finding friends on the Site, TVGorge allows users to search for other members using text searches, first and last name, email address, and other attributes. Users can invite friends to join TVGorge by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. TVGorge stores these email addresses so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to establish relationships between users. TVGorge does not sell invitation email addresses or use them for any other purpose. 

**Links to Third Party Sites** This Site contains links to other websites. Your use of linked websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked websites. 

**Security** TVGorge employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service. Such measures are reasonably designed to protect your information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. TVGorge uses password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your PII. 

**Policy Changes** TVGorge reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and will post any revisions on the Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last revised October 29th, 2009. 

If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@tvgorge.com.
